DETAILS:

sugarixi@gmail.com

+358452542229

https://sugarixi.github.io/Portfolio2/



CODING:

HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, React.JS, MySQL

SOFTWARE:

Visual Studio Code, Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Xd, GitHub

LANGUAGES:

Finnish – Native

English - Fluent

Hebrew - Basic communication skills

Tuire Nissinen

Front End Developer

BACKGROUND

My name is Tuire Nissinen. I'm a front end developer based in Finland. I learned the basics of HTML and CSS during my studies at Taitotalo. After graduating I have studied JavaScript and React.js independently through various online courses and by just trying things out! At the moment I'm working my way through Scrimba's front end developer career path to improve my skills in JavaScript and React. Additionally with quite a bit of customer service experience acquired I can handle anybody. Don't be afraid to hit me up!

EXPERIENCE

03.2020 - 06.2020 Angular Velocity Oy

Technical Writer

- Fixed-term project to write a user manual for <u>SPECTO Curling LIDAR</u> tracking system.
- Job included learning about the software and the product from the development team and translating it into a user-friendly manual.

2017 - 2019

APS - Air Parts, Services & Supplies

Sales Executive

- Locating aircraft parts from the global market using tools such as ILS,
 Stockmarket and PartsBase.
- Communicating and negotiating prices with suppliers over the phone and email.
- Working in a very fast-paced environment while meeting and exceeding the company's sales goals.

2010 - 2016

Alepa

Sales Assistant

- Assisting customers
- Working at the checkout
- Replenishing stock

EDUCATION

2019-2021

Taitotalo

Certificate of vocational qualification in business information technology

2013-2015

Omnia

Certificate of vocational qualification in cosmetology

2007-2010

Tapiolan aikuislukio

High School Diploma